JACKY ZHAO

OBJECTIVE

Technically sophisticated professional with solid experience in ensuring the alignment of web design and user experience requirements for optimizing web pages to achieve maximum efficiency. Demonstrated success in determining the structure and design of web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, resolving technical errors, and achieving customer satisfaction. Proficient troubleshooter with strong skills in diagnosing and resolving websites issues for improving websites through creative approach to front-end development.

Core Competencies

- Website Optimization
- Technical Troubleshooting
- Testing and Debugging
- Building Reusable codes

- Web User Interfaces
- Budget Administration
- Web Development Initiatives
- Quality Assurance

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCIES

Front End

- React JS, Redux
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Bootstrap, ¡Query
- AJAX, JSON, XML, APIs
- WordPress, Wix

Back End

- Node JS
- Express JS
- EJS
- MySQL
- MongoDB

Others

- Webpack
- Babel
- NPM, Git
- MS Office
- Adobe XD

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jr. Front-End Web Developer

Enspyre Interactive Inc., Markham (Dec 2019 – present)

Contribute experience in researching and analyzing new technologies and software applications for multiple projects and websites. Specialize in testing websites and performing troubleshooting to resolve technical issues prior to deployment.

- Develop dynamic cross-browser and cross-device web templates for clients to create multiple similar web pages using their own CMS.
- Develop promotional emails where it must be compatible with MS outlook.
- Collaborate with lead developer to develop projects for website throughout various phases of project lifecycle.

Freelance Web Developer

Toronto (10/2019 - Present)

Achieve client satisfaction by creating high-quality and targeted designs within budget and schedule guidelines. Collect, define, and translate user requirements into project designs and implementation plans. Strengthen identification of brand by crafting functional digital design concepts through various platforms.

- Successfully converted mockups into HTML, JavaScript, AJAX, and JSON within standards.
- Attained perpetual advancement by designing, implementing, and monitoring web pages and sites.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science: Mathematics, 09/2011 - 04/2019

McMaster University | Hamilton, Ontario

CERTIFICATIONS

Web Development, 05/2019 - 09/2019

Udemy - Online

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCIES Chinese | English